原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译：草草 Reginamoon 王大可 kahiko 想名字好难
翻译：JohnnyG Alex Lynn_宁   校对：某羽
时间轴：霜露   壬虚浪影  今
后期：斯人      总监：某羽
诉 讼 双 雄
第六季   第十四集
最新海外影视剧下载
《诉讼双雄》前情提要
Previously on Suits
不行
It's a no.
我以为你喜欢这个想法
I thought you liked the idea.
那是在我意识到它只会说点俏皮话和时评之前
That was before I realized that it was nothing but sassy remarks.
我还以为你想让孩子和它的生父
I thought you wanted our baby to have a relationship
能够建立感情
with its biological father.
但是如果你像今天这么激动的话
If you're gonna get this worked up,
让我觉得我根本不了解你
it makes me think I don't really know you.
要是我能让它更像你呢
What if I could make it more like you?
也许我能让它学到你的心
I might be able to give it the ability to learn from your heart.
你真的觉得这可能吗
You really think we could do that?
我觉得值得一试
We can try.
瑞秋・赞恩有资格成为律师
Rachel Zane deserves to be in the Bar.
你不仅不能阻止她
You're not only gonna stop blocking her,
如果有人阻止她你还要出面干预
you're gonna run interference for her if someone else does.
作为回报  你会做我让你做的事
And in return, you'll do what I want.
不  但我会为了其他事情帮你
No, but I'll do what you want for something else.
我们要对极速数据处理公司
We need to come up with a lawsuit
-提起诉讼  -不
- against Velocity Data Solutions. - No.
不行是什么意思
What do you mean, "No"?
制造诉讼来操控股价是违法的
Fabricating a lawsuit to manipulate a stock is illegal.
我们找个正当的诉讼理由就不算违法
It's not illegal if we find a legitimate suit.
我们把这差事搞定  恢复你的律师资格
Let's finish the job and get you back to being a lawyer.
"建筑施工需以证明书形式
"Tenants are required to be notified
通知所有租户"
of all construction by certified letter."
你说这算不算证明书
Is this a certified letter or not?
-反对  -这就是那个欺诈律师
- Objection. - Your Honor, this is the fraudulent attorney.
你再在庭上开口就会被逐出法庭
Open your mouth in my courtroom again and you will be removed.
格雷迪先生  你是否要反对
Mr. Grady, do you have an objection or not?
-我不反对  -那法庭别无选择
- I don't. - Then the court has no choice
只能判决有偏见驳回起诉
but to dismiss this case with prejudice.
那个阻止你面试的人
The guy holding up your interview
想让我们帮他办件事
was trying to get us to do something
因为他以为能威胁到我们
because he thought he could.
-那你要帮他办吗  -要
- Are you going to? - Yes.
-他要  -你说的是我想的那个意思吗
- He is. - Are you saying what I think you're saying?
我答应
I'm in.
好了  瑞秋已经走了
Okay, Rachel's gone.
别唬我
I don't want any bullshit.
告诉我  不管我们做什么
You're telling me that no matter what we do,
瑞秋都能当成律师
Rachel's getting into the Bar?
我能告诉你  如果她当不成
What I'm telling you is if she doesn't get in,
也绝不会是因为那个混蛋的阻拦
that asshole isn't gonna be the one that stopped her.
好  我答应
Okay. I'm in.
我们要做什么
What do we have to do?
我告诉你了
I told you what we need to do.
我们得拉低极速数据处理公司的股价
We need to make a dent in Velocity Data's stock.
哈维  这可不是小事
Harvey, that's no joke.
你知道我们得告他们多少钱
You realize how much we're gonna have to sue them for
才会产生这样的影响吧
to make their earnings take a hit?
当然了
You're damn right I do.
他们是家大公司
They're a huge company,
所以必须得是一记重拳
which means it's got to be something huge.
我都不确定那是否会有关系
I don't even know if that matters.
不管我们告他们什么
No matter what we sue them for,
他们都会想和解的
they're just gonna want to settle.
我知道
I know that.
所以我们得坚持他们承认有罪
Which means we need to insist on an admission of guilt.
我懂了
I get it.
你要我通过法律诊所来搞
You want me to run this whole thing through the clinic.
只有这样才能看上去合法合理
It's the only way to make it look legitimate.
哈维  我不知道我能不能说服纳森
Harvey, I don't know if I can convince Nathan to do that.
你最好说服他  如果有人发现
Well, you better, because if anyone figures out
我们是为了个人利益
that we're doing this for personal gain,
你就绝对当不成律师了
your chance of getting into the bar is gone.
等等  你还是合唱团的队长
Wait, you were Captain of the Glee Club?
正式职称是中校
The official title is Lieutenant Colonel,
但你不知道也没关系
but that's cool you didn't know that.
天啊  你17岁还戴牙套
Oh, my God. You still had braces at 17.
其实  我28岁又戴过
Actually, I had them again at 28.
这个  你的鼻道
Between this, your nasal passages,
皮肤治疗  还有足部手术
the skin tag epidemic and the foot surgeries,
你做过好多的手术啊
you really had a lot of medical procedures.
塔拉  我知道你在想什么
Tara, I know what you must be thinking
我发誓
and I swear,
我不会把我的毛病遗传给我们的孩子的
I will not pass any of my maladies onto our child.
路易  我没想那个
Louis, I wasn't thinking that,
但你知道生物角度讲
but you do understand that biologically
-这不是你的孩子吧  -当然
- this isn't your child. - Of course I do.
好
Okay.
但我是想  我们至少该要一个自己的孩子
But I was thinking we would have at least one child of our own.
至少
At least?
At least.
你是对的  路易
You were right, Louis.
了解彼此很好玩
Getting to know each other is fun.
你来了  太好了  我需要你帮忙
Good, you're here. I need your help.
是为了法拉盛工人赔偿的事吗
Is this about the worker comp case from Flushing?
不  是为了极速数据处理公司
No, this is about Velocity Data Solutions.
-他们怎么了  -他们不干净
- What about them? - They're a dirty company.
他们多年来干坏事不受惩罚
They've been getting away with shit for years.
我在皮尔逊-斯佩克特工作时一直不能找他们麻烦
I could never go after them when I worked at Pearson Specter
因为我们当时总是站在另一边的
because we were always on the other side of these things,
但我现在可以对他们追责了
but I can go after them now.
迈克  如果这需要我上庭
Mike, if this is going to require me going to court--
不会的
It's not.
奥利佛  我清楚那天发生的事
Look, Oliver, I know what happened the other day.
但你不上庭也可以做个好律师
But you don't have to be a trial lawyer to be a great lawyer.
什么意思
What are you saying?
我是说  你有其他律师没有的技艺
I'm saying that you have skills that other lawyers don't have
我会马上让你好好使用你的技艺
and I'm gonna put those skills to use right now.
-你需要什么  -那些箱子
- What do you need? - You see those boxes?
那是极速公司这20年来和解的所有案子
That's every case that Velocity has settled in the last 20 years
原告的名字都被封存了
where the names of the plaintiffs have been sealed.
我们得查明他们都是谁
We need to figure out who those people are,
他们收钱保了什么密
what they got paid not to say,
然后我们要让他们所有人出来作证
and then we need to get every damn one of them to come forward.
迈克  他们把你怎么了
Mike, what did these guys do to you?
他们没把我怎么样  奥利佛
They didn't do anything to me, Oliver.
我就是不喜欢别人认为
I just don't like it when people think
就因为没人注意
they can get away with anything
他们就可以为所欲为
just because nobody is watching.
-好快啊  -什么好快
- That was fast. - What was fast?
我以为你是来告诉我
Well, I assume you're here to tell me
你针对极速提起了诉讼
you filed suit against Velocity.
我来告诉你的是  克雷格
What I'm here to tell you, Craig,
是迈克・罗斯会处理极速的案子
is Mike Ross is gonna handle Velocity.
那我们就有问题了
Then we have a problem,
我可不是跟迈克・罗斯做的交易
'cause I didn't cut a deal with Mike Ross.
我是跟你做的交易
I cut a deal with you.
而你是企业法律顾问而我不是
And there's a reason you're an in-house counsel
-是有原因的  -什么意思
- and I'm not. - What are you talking about?
一旦我们丢下我们要丢的炸弹
Once we drop whatever bomb we're gonna drop,
他们肯定想和解  不认罪
they're gonna want to settle without an admission of guilt
大家都知道  我就专门和解
and everyone knows settling is what I do.
所以迈克・罗斯要把这事闹上法庭
So Mike Ross is gonna take this to court?
他都不是个律师
He's not even a goddamn lawyer.
这就对了  克雷格
Welcome to the conversation, Craig.
我就是来说这事
That's what I'm here to talk about.
你要搞定迈克的听证会
You're gonna make Mike's hearing official.
不行  这还太早
I can't do that, it's too soon.
扯淡  你以为我不知道
Bullshit. You think I don't know
你答应迈克的事只是为了让我帮你吗
you only said yes about Mike to get me to help you?
当然了
Of course that's why I said yes.
让他成为律师最难的部分
And the hardest thing about getting him into the Bar
是他没上过法学院  就没法为他安排听证会
is getting him a hearing when he hasn't even gone to law school.
所以你要为他担保
Which is why you're gonna sponsor him
因为他多年在皮尔逊-斯佩克特的工作
based on his years of work at Pearson Specter.
这是念法学
You're talking about reading the law.
没错
You're damn right I am.
这事有先例的  你清楚
There's precedent and you know it.
听着  我可以影响投票结果
Listen to me, I can influence the vote,
但我不能担保我要为他投票的人
but I cannot sponsor someone I'm going to be voting on.
那就找个能担保他的人
Then find someone who will.
你如果不能在下周内为他搞定听证会
Because if you can't get him a hearing in the next week,
这事就没戏了
this thing is off.
还有  克雷格
And one more thing, Craig.
你我不会再交谈了
You and I won't be talking again
因为如果你还没搞明白
because in case you haven't figured it out yet,
这已经比出轨
this is a hell of a lot more serious
要严重多了
than cheating on your wife.
诉讼双雄 第六季 第十四集
哈维  你怎么在这儿
Harvey, what are you doing in here?
什么意思  这是高管厨房
What do you mean? It's an executive kitchen.
-我是高管  -对  但你喜欢百吉饼
- I'm an executive. - Yeah, but you're a bagel guy.
这地方是羊角面包中心
This place is like croissant central.
或许我是来
Then maybe I just came in here
跟你共度美好时光的
hoping to spend some quality time with you.
你是说你想听听我跟塔拉度过的一夜吗
Are you saying you want to hear about my night with Tara?
当然
Of course I do.
不如我们先一起做做友谊手链
Right after we make friendship bracelets
然后再互相编编辫子
and braid each other's hair.
知会你一声  那是个神奇的夜晚
For your information, it was a magical evening,
但实际上  我是来谈正事的
but actually, I'm here to talk business.
-什么正事  -时尚定制公司
- What business? - Couture Apparel.
杰西卡和我总是会给他们的总裁做一份
Jessica and I always gave their CEO an annual analysis
来年法律需求的年度分析
of their legal needs for the upcoming year--
现在她走了  所以你想让我和你一起做
And now that she's gone, you want us to do it?
没错
Exactly.
感觉是在卖力推销啊
Sounds like a dog and pony show.
不止于此  哈维
It is more than that, Harvey.
这是为了展现实力
It is a show of force.
在那天  我们得让卡莉・唐纳休觉得
For one day, Carly Donahue needs to feel like
自己是我们最重要的客户
the most important client in the portfolio.
只派一位合伙人过去
And having one partner go by himself
不足以传达这个信息
doesn't send that message.
路易  放松  我很乐意去
Lewis, relax. I'm happy to do it.
真的吗
You are?
当然了  告诉过你了  我们是搭档
Of course I am. I told you, we're partners.
你知道吗  哈维  我一直梦想着能像这样
You know, Harvey, I always dreamed it could be like this.
搭档  蓝颜知己  朋友
Partners, confidantes, friends.
我也有同样的梦想  路易
I had the exact same dream, Lewis.
-真的吗  -不  假的
- Really? - No, not really.
意思是不是你永远也不会和我去泡泥浴
Does that mean you're never gonna go mudding with me?
没错  路易  就是这个意思
Yes, Lewis, that's what it means.
我会把会面细节告诉唐娜
I'll give Donna the details on that meeting.
希望你准备好了
Hey, I hope you got a hammer,
我给你带来了些材料
'cause I just brought you some nails.
-你有所发现吗  -是的
- You found something? - Yeah, I did.
我已经找到了六起可利用的案子
I already found six cases we can use,
而那只是冰山一角
and that's just the tip of the iceberg.
所以我们穿好衣服  去狠揍极速一顿吧
So let's grab our coats and go kick Velocity's ass up and down the street.
淡定点  泰森
Easy, Tyson.
你得告诉我这些都是什么类型的诉讼
You have to tell me what kind of suits these are.
都是矿业诉讼
They're mining suits,
意味着健康问题或是企业疏忽...
which means health problems or corporate negligence--
无论是哪种  造成的危害都很大
Either way, the damages could be through the roof.
奥利佛  做得好
Oliver, this is great.
我知道  虽然...
I know. And...
假如你让我据此在庭上抗辩
if you asked me to make an argument about it in court,
我八成会搞砸
I'd probably shit the bed.
但是  迈克  我告诉你
But, Mike, I'm telling you,
这件事大有文章
there's something here.
我也要告诉你
And I'm telling you,
也许有一天你能克服你的上庭恐惧症
maybe one day you'll overcome your court stuff,
也许你克服不了
maybe you won't.
无论是哪种
Either way,
这些都足以证明你是个好律师了
this proves that you're a hell of a lawyer.
是啊  谢了  迈克
Yeah, thanks, Mike.
我必须承认
I gotta admit,
发现自己能做到这样让我感觉挺良好的
it feels pretty good to know I can do what I just did.
那你不如去起草诉讼吧
Then why don't you start drafting a suit.
因为等我说服这些人参与进来之后
'Cause after I get these people on board,
我们就要准备起诉了
that's exactly what we're gonna have to do.
唐娜  你绝对猜不到刚刚路易想求我做什么
Donna, you're never gonna believe what Louis just asked me.
让我猜三次
Give me three guesses.
他想成为你  他想看上去和你一样
He wants to be you. He wants to look like you.
他想穿上你这副皮囊
He wants to wear your skin as a body suit.
好吧  你刚刚是不是没开口就说了这堆
Okay, did you just talk without saying anything?
这有什么新鲜的  你整天这么做
What's the big deal? You do it all the time.
说得好  唐娜  你今天如有神助
Good one, Donna. You're on fire today.
好吧  这到底是怎么回事
Okay, what the hell's going on here?
你是说真・唐娜吗
Oh, you mean The Donna?
这只是本杰明和我在合作的一个小产品
It's just a little product that Benjamin and I have been working on.
虽然它还不具备我的情商
It doesn't have my emotional intelligence yet
但我觉得我还是可以拿它来玩玩的
but I thought I'd have a little fun with it in the meantime.
你都有情商了吗
Do you have your emotional intelligence yet?
等它能回这句  那才叫有什么
When it can top that, you might have something.
窝囊废
Loser.
好的  那句话是谁说的
Okay, which one of you said that?
-她说的  -她说的
- She did. - She did.
抱歉  伙计  本店关门了
Sorry, buddy. Grill's shut down.
要到下午五点才开门
We don't open again till five.
没关系  我不是来吃芝士汉堡的
That's okay. I'm not here for a cheeseburger.
我是来谈谈黑泽顿矿业公司的
I'm here to talk about Hazelton Mining Company.
怎么了
What about it?
你以工作导致威胁生命的健康问题为由
You filed a complaint alleging life-threatening health problems
提出过控告
resulting from work.
那次控告神秘地消失了
That complaint mysteriously went away
而我希望帮助你获得你应得的赔偿
and I want to help you get the compensation that you deserve.
我不需要一个唯利是图的律师的帮助
I don't need any help from an ambulance chaser.
我不是那种唯利是图的律师  斯塔摩斯先生
I'm not an ambulance chaser, Mr. Stamos.
我叫迈克・罗斯  我在一家法律诊所工作
My name is Mike Ross, I work at a clinic
我们的佣金上限为五万美元
and our commissions are capped at $50,000.
所以我们做这个不是为了钱
So we are not in this for the money.
那是为了什么
Then what are you in it for?
这么说吧  极速公司不是好东西
Let's just say Velocity is bad news.
我很想帮你
Well, I'd like to help,
但即便我想起诉那帮混蛋  我也不能
but even if I wanted to sue those bastards, I can't.
我知道
I know.
你拿了一笔钱  然后签了保密协议
You took a payout and you signed a non-disclosure agreement.
不是因为这个
That's got nothing to do with it.
他们让我们所有人都签了那玩意
They made us all sign those things.
假如我们中的任何一人违约了
If any one of us breaks it,
那所有人的协议就都无效了
it negates them all.
那就让它们无效啊
Then negate them all.
你说得倒容易
That's easy for you to say.
我快要死了  而死因太长一串了
I'm dying of something with a name so long,
我都没办法说给你听
I can't even tell you what it is.
而你所说的你们佣金的上限
And you're talking about your fee being capped
已经超过了他们付给我的钱
at more money than they paid me.
听我说  假如他们真的只给了你这么点钱
Listen to me, if that's really all they paid you,
而你又真的快死了
and you really are dying,
我们几秒钟就能解除那些保密协议
we can shatter those NDAs in about five seconds.
你不明白
You don't understand.
我是他们的监工  罗斯先生
I was their supervisor, Mr. Ross.
那些人患病都是我的负责
I was responsible for all those guys that got sick
而正是我同意了只收那么点钱
and I'm the one that got us the money
就签保密协议
that went with those NDAs.
让我猜猜
And let me guess:
自从你签了协议
ever since you signed them,
你就没睡过一晚上好觉
you haven't had a good night's sleep.
如果你说我说错了  我马上就走
Tell me I'm wrong, I'll leave right now.
需要我做些什么
What do I have to do?
瑞秋  怎么了
Rachel, what are you doing here?
-我能进去吗  -当然
- Can I come in? - Of course.
要喝点什么吗
Can I get you something?
不用了  谢谢
No, I'm good. Thank you.
假如你是来视察你的婚礼场地的
If this is about checking out the place for your wedding,
那还是白天看效果比较好
it might be better during the day.
不  我不是来谈那个的
No, I didn't come to talk about that.
我是来谈这个的
I came here to talk about this.
瑞秋  这真是太棒了
Rachel, this is terrific.
你甚至都不用去面试
You passed the Character and Fitness committee
就通过了品行考核委员会的审核
without even having to go in.
是啊
I know.
那你为何看起来如此忧虑
Then why do you look so concerned?
因为我知道你和迈克为了这个结果所做的事
Because I know what you and Mike are doing to make this happen.
瑞秋  这封信和我和迈克做的事没有任何关系
Rachel, this letter has nothing to do with what we're doing.
这是你应得的  这家伙做的事也是应该的
You deserve this and all this guy is doing is the right thing.
好吧  就算你说得对
Okay, let's say that's true.
那你们俩为了让迈克有同样结果
What about what you two are doing to make
-做的那些事呢  -听我说
- the same thing happen for Mike? - Listen--
不  哈维  你听我说
No, Harvey, I need you to listen.
他刚刚在监狱里呆了几个月
He just spent the past couple months in prison,
而且原本是要呆几年的
and it was supposed to be years.
我绝不能让这种事再发生
And I can't let that happen again.
不会再发生的
It's not going to happen again.
我知道不会  所以我才会来
I know it isn't. Which is why I'm here.
我需要你向我保证如果事情进展的不顺利
I need your word that if things start to go south,
你一定要及时叫停
that you will pull the plug on this whole thing.
-瑞秋  -哈维  我要你保证
- Rachel. - Harvey, I want your word.
我保证
You got it.
如果不顺利  就终止
Thing go south, it's done.
-迈克  你有时间吗  -有  怎么了
- Hey, Mike, you got a second? - Yeah, what's up?
我正要问你呢
I was hoping you could tell me.
很显然奥利佛已经在会议室呆了一天了
Apparently Oliver was in the conference room all day
在处理一件诉极速数据的案子
working on some case against Velocity Data.
是的  我分给他的任务
Uh, yeah, I gave him an assignment.
什么叫你给他的任务
What do you mean you "Gave him an assignment"?
他要处理劳工赔偿的案子
He had the workers comp case.
我帮他处理了
I took care of that.
迈克  你的工作不是产生新案子
Mike, your job isn't to generate cases.
而是针对现有的案子提供咨询
It's to consult on the cases we've already taken.
我知道
I know that,
但也包括让我们的员工成为更好的律师
but it's also to help our associates become better lawyers.
奥利佛之前在庭上被打击了
Oliver got his ass kicked in court the other day.
我只是在帮他重新建立信心
I'm just helping to build him back up.
我们手上有很多案子
And there are plenty of other cases
都能帮他达到这个目的
you could've used to do that.
但你却跑去签了一个集体诉讼
Instead, you went and you signed a class action,
我们从来不接那些案子
which is something we do not do.
我们为什么不接呢
Well, why isn't it something we do?
这些人正在经历致命的疾病
These men have life-threatening health problems
他们需要一个人来为他们奔走
They need someone to give a shit about them.
我们不接这类案子
It isn't something we do
是因为我们没有时间和人手
because we don't have the time or the man power
去扳倒一个像极速那样的巨头
to take on a giant like Velocity.
纳森  我不知道你想听到什么答案
Nathan, I don't know what you want me to say.
我出去走了走  签了这些人  他们也信任我
I went out there, I signed these guys and they trusted me.
我不能现在退出
I can't back out now.
你在皮尔逊-斯佩克特
This the kinda shit you pulled
也会做类似的事吗
when you were at Pearson Specter?
偶尔吧
On occasion.
那我想听到你说下次
Then I want you to say the next time you think
你要做类似的事情之前
to pull something like this,
你至少要出于尊重提前告诉我一声
you have the common courtesy to tell me before you do it.
我建议你泡个热水澡外加一大盒冰淇淋
I suggest a warm bubble bath and a pint of Chunky Monkey.
因为如果你自己都不疼爱自己
Because if you're not good to yourself,
怎么能指望别人对你好呢
how can you expect anyone else to be good to you?
顺便说一句
And for your information,
程式首选的建议是香草豆和恩雅的专辑
the initial program was vanilla bean and an Enya CD,
但这是跟你学的
but it learned from you.
是不是很棒棒
Pretty awesome, right?
不  本杰明  没有很棒
No, Benjamin, it's not pretty awesome.
你不能讲这些陈词滥调
You can't just give it platitudes.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
感同身受的重点是
The key to having empathy
让人们感到获得了支持
is making people feel supported in their feelings,
并不只是帮他们解决问题
not just trying to solve their problems.
这是我听过最蠢的说法了
That is the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
不是的  而且不仅如此
No, it isn't. And not only that,
你还要针对这个人的感受
you have to tailor its response
给出量身定制的答案
to the feelings the person is having.
那要怎么才能做到
How am I supposed to do that?
你必须让它学会聆听
You have to have it listen.
好吧  我懂了
Okay, I get it.
你是在说它必须要理解用户的感受
You're saying it has to understand the feelings of its user,
然后再用一种同情的方式表达这种理解
and express that understanding in a sympathetic manner.
正是  你觉得你能做到吗
Exactly. Now, you think you can do that?
当然可以  我只需要
Of course I can. All I need to do
让它持续不断地接触目前所没有的东西
is continually expose it to what it's not providing
最终的反馈回路就会
and eventually the feedback loop will show it
告诉他如何变得更像你
how to be more like you.
也就是变得无与伦比
In other words, awesome.
是的  这才是终极目标
Yes, that's the entire point of this exercise.
还要说一句
And for the record,
无与伦比的人不会听恩雅
no one awesome listens to Enya.
好吧  也许确实不会听她的晚期作品
Well maybe not her later work.
你们就一个人吗
You're the whole team?
看起来挺公平  你也只有一个呀
Seems fair. There's only one of you.
我不是律师  罗斯先生
I'm not an attorney, Mr. Ross.
-我是首席执行官  -看来你是来真的
- I'm CEO. - Then you must be serious.
你开个价吧
Why don't you give me a number?
你想听价格  零
You want a number? Zero.
因为我是不会被你这样的人勒索的
'Cause I'm not gonna be shaken down by the likes of you.
这不是勒索  帕默先生
This isn't a shakedown, Mr. Palmer.
那些人因为你们公司知情的情况
Those men are dying from conditions
而正在面临死亡
that your company knew about.
那些人已经签了保密协议
Those men signed non-disclosure agreements.
如果他们不遵守
And if they break them,
我们可以要回所有的钱
we can come after them for every penny they got.
但我有办法让所有协议都无效
And I've got a way to bust every damn one of those agreements.
不可能  那些协议非常严密
No way, those things are airtight.
如果是被迫签订的协议就谈不上严密了
Airtight doesn't apply when signed under duress,
所谓被迫正是指罹患肺癌
which is exactly what dying of lung cancer
但无法支付医药费的情况
and not being able to afford a doctor is.
那祝你好运重复这种申辩一千次
Well good luck making that argument a thousand times,
因为我会尽全力
because I'm gonna fight each and every one of them
-逐一回击的 -这是集体诉讼  你不能这么做
- to my dying breath. - You can't do that,they're a class. -
我可以也一定会
I can and I will.
你再继续纠缠的话
And you move forward with this,
我会用无数的文案工作
I'm gonna bury that shit-hole legal clinic
把你那个可怜的法律诊所埋掉
of yours in so much paperwork, you're going to choke to death.
所以你把我叫来只是为了当面拒绝我
So you just called me down here to tell me no to my face?
我把你叫来是为了告诉你
I called you down here to show you that
如果你继续这个案子
if you pursue this action,
那些人和你最终都会一无所有
those men are going to beleft with nothing and so are you.
这策略可真不错
That's a hell of a strategy,
那你肯定没有收到我的备忘录
but I guess you didn't get the memo
我的联席律所是皮尔逊-斯佩克特-利特
that my co-counsel on this is Pearson Specter Litt.
胡说  他们的名字没有出现在任何文件上
Bullshit. Their name's not on any one of these documents.
因为他们想保持低调
'Cause they wanted to keep a low profile,
但你可以去确认  我也会亲自给他们打电话的
but go ahead, pick up the phone. I'll call them myself.
那我就要和你还有你的大律所在法庭上见了
Then I guess I'll see you and your big law firm in court.
因为正如我所说
Because like I said,
我不会被你这样的人勒索的
I'm not gonna be shaken down by the likes of you.
哈维  我刚接到
Harvey, I just got a phone call
极速公司律师的电话
from the lawyers at Velocity,
他们想确认我们是迈克的联席律师
They wanted me to confirm that we're co-counsel with Mike on this.
那你怎么回答的
What'd you tell them?
你觉得我会怎么回复  我告诉他们没问题
What do you think I told them? I told them yes.
因为如果他们问  说明他在虚张声势
Because if they're asking, he obviously bluffed
我不会放任他不管的
and I'm not gonna hang him out to dry.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我要去搞清楚他做了什么和为什么这么做
I'm gonna find out what he did and why he did it.
-你到底在搞什么  -冷静  哈维
- What the hell did you do? - Relax, Harvey,
我正准备来告诉你
I was just coming to tell you-- -
不  我明确说过
No, I specifically said
我不能被别人知道牵扯进了这件事
that I can't be seen to be involved in this thing.
你还说过我们只有一次机会
And you also said we only had one shot at this.
当时我在场和这个人谈的
I was the one in the room with this guy.
-他知道他看透我了  -那又怎样
- He had me and he knew it. - So what?
是你一直说如果我在一场肉搏战中
So you always said that if I'm in a knife fight
处于劣势  那就举起枪
and I'm losing, to pick up a gun.
皮尔逊-斯佩克特-利特就是那把枪
And Pearson Specter Litt is a goddamn gun.
我知道这和我们想要的不完全一样
Look, I know this isn't exactly what we wanted,
但我依然可以坚持认罪
but I can still be the one to insist on an admission of guilt,
所以说到底怎么了
so what's really going on here?
我答应瑞秋如果风险太大
I promised Rachel that if this thing got too risky
我就停手  现在风险更进一步了
I'd pull the plug, and it just got a hell of a lot riskier.
这也变得更真实了
Well, it also got real.
那些矿工需要我们
Those miners need us.
我不会抛弃他们的  所以
I'm not going to abandon them, so...
你想干什么
what do you wanna do?
你觉得我想干什么
What do you think I want to do?
我想好好收拾收拾这家伙
I wanna kick this guy's ass.
那现在的情况是  我有150名矿工入伙
Then here's the situation: I got a 150 miners on board
我还能废除保密协议
and I can bust the NDAs.
但我无法提出集体诉讼
But I can't make the action a class
因为他们已经签字放弃这个权利了
'cause they already signed those rights away.
我懂了
I get it.
他以为我们不可能把所有案子分开提交法院
He doesn't think we can get all those separate cases to court.
那他又要面临新问题了
Well, he's got another thing coming.
我楼上有十个新律师
I got ten brand-new associates upstairs
在求着要做这种案子
begging to work on a case like this.
你得指导所有人
You're gonna oversee every single one of them
哪怕要一整晚
if it takes all night.
那我一小时以后去你办公室见你
Then I have to meet you at your office in an hour.
我有点事得先去处理好
Something I need to take care of first.
路易  不管你想说什么  都得先等等
Louis, whatever it is, it's gonna have to wait.
不用  我很快就能说完
No, this'll just take a second.
是关于见卡莉・唐纳休的事
It's about the Carly Donahue meeting.
-我在想  -路易  对不起
- I was thinking-- - Louis, I'm sorry,
但我去不了了
but I'm not gonna be able to make it.
-什么  为什么  -迈克有个案子要我帮忙
- What? Why the hell not? - Mike needs my help on a case.
哈维  你可能不想听这个
Harvey, you may not want to accept this,
但是迈克已经不在这里工作了
but Mike doesn't work here anymore.
律所的事是最重要的
and firm business takes priority over--
路易  这次是律所的事
Listen, Louis, this is firm business
而且如果我预想的事发生了
and if what I think is gonna happen happens,
迈克就会回来了
Mike's gonna end up back here when it's done.
-什么  -你还记得
- What? - You remember that thing
我们帮瑞秋解决的那件事吗
that we took care of for Rachel
你说这可能值得一试
that you said might be worth doing?
看来结果确实如此
Well, it turns out it was worth doing.
只不过我是帮迈克做
Only I'm doing it for Mike.
天哪  赛德尔同意帮他了
Holy shit. Seidel agreed to go to bat for him?
是的  这件事搞定后迈克拿到律师资格
Yes, and once it's done  and Mike's in the Bar,
他就能回来工作了
he can come back here and work again.
哈维  这太棒了
Harvey, that is great
没人比我更想看到这个结果了
and nobody wants that more than I do,
-但这只是一次会面  -路易  我知道
- but it's just one meeting. - Louis, I know that,
但三个小时后  我就要连续三天
but in about three hours, I'm gonna be under water
-都无法抽身的  -哈维
- for the next three days. - Harvey--
路易  我知道我说过会和你一起去
Louis, I know I told you I'd be there for you,
但我也需要你支持我
but I need you to be there for me.
好吧  哈维  我会的
Okay, Harvey, I'll do it.
太好了  你还在  收拾好极速公司的文件
Good, you're still here. Box up the Velocity files
-然后在楼下等我  -我们要去哪
- and meet me downstairs. - Where are we going?
皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所同意跟我们合作这个案子
Pearson Specter agreed to partner up on the case.
-天哪  这可是个大事  -想加入吗
- Shit, that's big. - Want in?
当然想  给我十分钟
Hell yeah. Give me ten minutes.
-你  -怎么了
- Hey. - Yeah?
你能告诉我这是什么吗
You wanna tell me what this is?
这是一份合伙代理的协议书
That is an agreement to co-counsel
我正准备告诉你这件事
and I was just gonna come tell you about it.
你准备背着我干多少事
How many times are you gonna make a move without telling me?
纳森  对不起  但我得赶快下手
Nathan, I'm sorry, but I had to move fast.
因为极速公司的人在给我施加压力
The guy at Velocity was putting the screws to me.
这里面有什么见不得人的勾当吗  迈克
Is something shady going on here, Mike?
什么
What?
你先是突然搞来了这么大的案子
First you bring in this huge case out of the blue.
然后眨眼之间又牵扯来了你的老东家
Then all of sudden, you're bringing in your old firm.
是你说我们的资源不足以
You're the one who said we didn't have the resources
解决这种事情
to handle this sort of thing,
所以我才拉来了有能力解决问题的人
so I just brought in someone who would.
没错  我敢说他们也会从中分得一杯羹
Yeah, and I bet they're getting a sweet deal out of it.
不是这样的
It's not like that.
他们收取正常费用的一半
They're taking half their usual fee.
-只要这么多  -那你呢  迈克
- That's all they're getting. - And what about you, Mike?
-你能得到什么好处  -你什么意思
- What are you getting? - What are you talking about?
你敢说你没有把这个案件
You're gonna tell me you're not using this
当做回你老东家的跳板
as a stepping stone to get back to your old firm?
什么  当然没有  纳森  我不想回去
What? No, Nathan, I don't want to go back there.
扯淡  我不相信你
Bullshit. I don't believe you.
这里面肯定有问题  我能感觉得到
Something is going on here and I know it.
你知道吗  纳森
You know what, Nathan?
我告诉你吧  哈维・斯佩克特之前像你一样
For your information, Harvey Specter did offer me
邀请我回去做顾问
a consulting job just like you did,
但他给我的工资是你给的十倍
except his had one more zero at the end of it,
可我还是拒绝他了
and I still turned him down.
是我选择来这里
I chose to be here,
但我不想一到关键时刻就被猜疑
but I don't want to be second-guessed at every turn.
所以你要么相信
So either you're gonna trust that
我是为了你好  要么别信我
my heart is in the right place or you're not.
好吧  那我也告诉你  迈克
Well, for your information, Mike,
我现在也没有别的选择
right now I really don't have a choice.
-你还好吗  -我不好
- Hey, are you okay? - No, I'm not okay.
我到底要怎么才能
How the hell am I supposed to
单枪匹马保住卡莉・唐纳休的业务
keep Carly Donahue's business all by myself?
路易  你是管理合伙人
Because, Louis, you're co-managing partner
而且你还是个厉害的律师
and you're one hell of a lawyer.
你不明白  是不是
Oh, you just don't get it, do you?
这个女人想知道自己对我们律所很重要
This woman wants to know that she's special to this firm.
如果只有我一个人去
If I walk in there by myself,
她会一边嘲笑我一边走出会议室
she's gonna laugh me out of the room.
那你为什么不把这话跟哈维说
Then why didn't you tell that to Harvey?
因为我知道迈克对他的重要性
Because I know how important Mike is to him
我也不想让他失望
and I didn't want to let him down.
-那就别让他失望  -这不是
- Then don't. - That is not--
路易  不只有这一个办法
Louis, if this woman needs to know she's special to us,
能让这个女人知道她对我们的重要性
there's more than one wayto do it
哈维并不是你唯一的选择
and Harvey's not the only one you can bring.
唐娜  你的想法很好  但是会议在明天
Donna, that's great. But this meeting is tomorrow
可我还不了解这些新律师同事
and I don't even know these new associates yet.
你了解的  你了解卡特里娜
Yes, you do. You know Katrina,
她不仅仅是新同事  她还是初级合伙人
who's not just a new associate, she's a Junior Partner
你也了解瑞秋  她和四年律师一样优秀
and you know Rachel, who's as good as a fourth-year.
你到那里显示出这样的力量
You go there with a show of force like that,
相信我  这个女人会折服的
trust me, this woman is gonna be blown away.
好的  唐娜  就显示力量这个方法了
Okay, Donna. Show of force it is.
天啊  奥蒂斯・雷丁的第一张唱片
Holy shit, Otis Redding's first album?
你确定哈维不介意我拿出来吗
You sure Harvey won't mind if I take it out?
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
他不会介意的  他说如果收藏不是供大家看的
No, he says if that collection's not for everyone,
那收藏还有什么意义呢
then what's the point of even having it here?
-听起来像个很棒的人  -最棒的
- Sounds like a great guy. - The best.
甘地在这  哈维在这
Ghandi. Harvey.
-你认真的吗  -向上帝发誓
- You serious? - Hand to God.
他简直就是个圣人
Man's practically a saint.
-发生什么了  -奥利佛  这是哈维・斯佩克特
- What's going on? - Oliver, Harvey Specter.
哈维・斯佩克特  这是奥利佛
Harvey Specter, Oliver.
见到你很高兴  奥利佛
Nice to meet you, Oliver.
要我给你倒一杯吗
Would you like me to pour you a drink?
-真的吗  -当然不是
- Would you? - No, I wouldn't.
现在把那唱片放下  然后滚出我的办公室
Now put that down, get out of my office
如果我再抓到你碰我的任何东西
and if I ever catch you touching one of my things again,
-我就把它塞到你屁股里  -他认真的吗
- I'll shove it up your ass. - Is he serious?
屁股那部分不是认真的
Oh, not about the ass part,
但是如果是我  我会把它放回去的
but I'd put it back.
你玩我
You set me up.
欢迎来到皮尔逊-斯佩克特-利特律所
Welcome to Pearson Specter Litt.
你享受这么玩吗
You enjoy that?
-还不错吧  -很好
- Yeah, it felt okay. - Good.
现在  你为什么不去确保
Now why don't you go make sure
每个人都知道他们在做什么呢
everyone knows exactly what they're doing
现在已经晚上9点了  时间不等人
It's 9 p.m., the clock's ticking
我们得把这件事搞定
and we gotta get this thing done.
你准备怎么做
What are you gonna do?
我想一想怎么和
I'm gonna figure out what we're going
当极速数据处理公司的那混蛋
to say to that Velocity son of a bitch
明天走进来求着签和解协议时  我们应该怎么说
when he walks in here tomorrow begging for a settlement.
你知道这是要干什么吗
Do you have any idea what this is about?
格蕾琴说路易要分配给我们一些特殊的任务
Gretchen said that Louis had some special assignment for us.
我只知道我收到了一条关于那不勒斯冰激凌的
All I know is I got a rambling voicemail
含糊不清的语音留言
about Neapolitan ice cream.
那不勒斯冰激凌
Neapolitan ice cream?
是的  巧克力  香草和草莓的完美混合
Yes. Chocolate and vanilla melded beautifully with strawberry.
就像我们将要为卡莉・唐纳休做的一样
Just like we're about to do for Carly Donahue.
路易  你刚刚是把我叫做巧克力吗
Louis, did you just call me chocolate?
我为什么那样做  你是我的白天鹅
Why would I do that? You're my white swan,
卡特里娜是我的黑天鹅  有那么难明白吗
Katrina's my black swan. The math ain't that hard.
盒子里是什么  路易
What's with the boxes, Louis?
这是律所为时尚定制公司做过的一切
This is everything the firm has ever done for Couture Apparel.
你要带我们去年会
You're taking us to your annual meeting?
我不仅仅是带你们
I'm not just taking you.
-我们要一起做这件事  -好的  路易
- We're running it together. - Okay, Louis--
我知道你们在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
一个初级合伙人和一个法学院三年级的学生到底
How the hell are a Junior Partner and a third-year law student
是如何填进杰西卡的13号鞋呢
supposed to fill Jessica's size 13s?
答案是  你们不能
Well the answer is: you can't.
-没人可以  -那我们为什么来这
- No one can. - Then why are we here?
因为以前我们常常用等级来迷住卡莉
Because we used to dazzle Carly with rank.
今年  我们准备用事实说话
This year, we're gonna dazzle her with substance.
让她知道我们比其他人更了解她的生意
By knowing her business better than anyone else.
我来搞定生意
I'll take care of the business.
你俩要做的是为她量身定制个
What you two are gonna do is personally tailor
幻灯片展示
the presentation to her.
截至目前  我们还有不到24小时的时间
And as of now, we have less than 24 hours to do that.
-我们不会让你失望的  路易  -我知道你们不会的
- We won't let you down, Louis. - I know you won't.
你觉得杰西卡真的穿13码吗
You think Jessica really wears size 13s?
这也正是我在思考的问题
That's exactly what I was thinking.
奥利佛  怎么样了
Oliver, how's it going?
还好
It's going okay.
我已经起草了6份投诉
I'm finished drafting six complaints.
怎么了
What is it?
没什么  只是我做6份的时间
It's nothing, it's just, in the time I did six,
他们大多数已经做了9份或10份了
most of them did nine or ten.
我猜那意味着你已经到冲刺阶段了
I guess that means you're in the home stretch, huh?
可能吧
Guess I am.
奥利佛  我知道你在想什么
Look, Oliver, I know what you're thinking.
但是我告诉纳森的是实话
But I was telling Nathan the truth.
我没在想办法回来和这些家伙一起工作
I'm not looking to come back here with these guys
并放弃你们
instead of working with you.
我知道你不想回来  迈克
I know you don't wanna come back here, Mike.
我只是想说  这些律师很厉害
I guess I just wanted to say these associates are bad ass,
我很感激你选择和我这样的人一起工作
and I appreciate you choosing to work with someone like me
而不是他们
over them.
你介意我问一下  你是怎么如此确定
You mind if I ask how you're so sure
我不想回到这呢
I don't want to come back here?
因为这些律师都很厉害
Because these associates are amazing lawyers,
但是一整晚没有一个人提到
but not a single one of them mentioned an actual human being
案子中的人
involved in this case the whole night.
他们只想赢
They're just trying to win.
那没有错
And there's nothing wrong with that,
但那不是你的风格
but that's not you.
是的  奥利佛  但那样做是有问题的
Yeah, Oliver, there is something wrong with that.
所以你会成为比他们任何人
And that's why you're gonna be a better lawyer
都更好的律师
than any one of these guys.
我去告诉哈维我们进入冲刺阶段了
I'm gonna go tell Harvey that we're in the home stretch.
-怎么样了  天才  -什么
- How's it going, genius? - What?
我说  怎么样了
I said, how's it going?
我来告诉你怎么样了
I'll tell you how it's going.
-这是行不通的  -什么
- It's not going to work. - What?
-但是我以为你说...  -我不在乎你怎么想
- But I thought that you said-- - I don't care what you thought.
这不是《西部世界》  我不能使她人性化
This isn't "Westworld." I can't make her human.
本杰明  我没有让你把她变得人性化
Benjamin, I'm not asking you to make her human.
我只是希望你给她点同情心
I'm just asking you to give her a little compassion.
我不知道该怎么做
Well I don't know how to do that.
它应该自我学习的  但是它没有
And it's supposed to learn from itself, but it isn't.
怎么了
what's going on?
我一直告诉自己
The story I always told myself was the only reason
我没有在硅谷工作的唯一原因是我不想去
I didn't work in Silicon Valley was that I didn't want to,
但事实是  我没有去那工作的能力
but the truth is, I don't have what it takes.
你走进来  叫我天才
And then you come in here, calling me a genius and--
本杰明  没事的
Benjamin, it's okay.
你只是个普通人
You're only human.
如果行不通的话  那就行不通吧
If it doesn't work, it doesn't work.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Really.
此外  如果我不能对你有同情心
Besides, if I can't show you compassion,
那我怎么指望真・唐娜也有同情心呢
how can I ever expect The Donna to show compassion?
谢谢你  唐娜
Thanks Donna.
我很抱歉  我让你失望了
I'm sorry if I got your hopes up.
想好明天我们怎么说了吗
Figure out what we're going to say tomorrow?
你收到那些投诉啦
You get those complaints ready?
你先回答我的问题
I asked you first.
你说得对  但可不是我让
Yeah, but I'm not the one
手下那群我见过的最菜的律师
who had the least experienced lawyer I've ever met
到最后关头才把东西整理好的
put this thing over the goal line.
拜托  我才是你见过的
Come on, I thought I was the least experienced lawyer
最没经验的律师好吧
you've ever met.
不  你是我见过的最菜的白痴
No, you were the least experienced dickhead I ever met.
-好吧  -因为那个孩子或许没什么经验
- Right. - Because that kid may be green,
但他是你们两个之中
but he's the only one of you two
唯一读过法律专业的
that actually went to law school.
我又不是不知道
Don't I know it.
迈克  你在想什么
Mike, what's on your mind?
没什么  只是在想  我们做的这件事
Nothing. It's just-- this whole thing we're doing
让我对好多人撒谎了  包括奥利弗
is making me lie to a lot of people, including Oliver
然而我并不喜欢对人撒谎
and I'm not thrilled about it.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
纳森认为这件案子有外部动因
Nathan thinks there's an ulterior motive
而且他猜得不错
to this case and he's right.
奥利弗也发现了  我不得不对他们撒谎
Oliver saw it and I had to lie to them both to cover it up.
或许这是真的
Maybe that's true,
但是你不能被这些分心了
but you need to keep your eye on the ball.
你是值得获得律师资格的
You deserve to be a lawyer.
而且你也是在帮助那些矿工
You're doing good for those miners
-这些才是最重要的  -我不确定  哈维
- and that's all that matters. - I don't know, Harvey.
你那么关心这孩子的想法是为什么呢
What do you care so much about what this kid thinks anyway?
因为是他让我改变主意
Because he's the reason I decided to change my mind
决定做这件事的
about doing this whole thing.
-什么意思  -他人品很好
- What do you mean? - He's a great kid.
而且他以后也会成为一个好律师
And he's gonna be a great lawyer.
但是我只能眼睁睁地看着他输了案子
But I had to watch him tank a case without being
我没法帮他  而一个女人也因此流落街头
able to help him and a woman ended up out on the street.
我想如果我们做成这个案子的话
I thought if we do this, then I'll never to have to sit back
我就不用再眼睁睁地
and do nothing when someone I care about
看着我在乎的人输了
is losing ever again.
那么就不要再为我们做的事瞎担心了
Then stop worrying about what we're doing
因为明天我们不会输
because tomorrow isn't about losing.
我们要赢
It's about winning.
太扯了
This is ridiculous.
我们辛苦了一晚上  什么都没找到
We've been up all night and we've got nothing.
-不  我们有收获  -这是什么
- Yes, we do. - What is this?
这是留住卡莉・唐纳休的业务的关键
This is the key to keeping Carly Donahue's business.
三年前和《美食家杂志》的旧访谈
How is a three-year-old interview
怎么可能帮到我们
with "Gourmand Magazine" Going to help us?
因为这说明了她是个吃货
Because it shows she's a foodie.
就和路易说的一样  我们需要让她看到
And like Louis said, we need to show her
我们不仅对她的公司业务了如指掌  还了解她
that we don't only understand her company, we understand her.
我知道了
I get it.
那我们把展示框架
What if we structured the presentation
搭成九道菜品  并给每道菜
like a nine course meal and paired a discrete piece
配上独立的法律分析怎么样
of legal analysis with each course?
就像搭配红酒测试一样
Like a paired wine tasting.
是一对一的红酒测试
Coupled with a paired wine tasting.
等等  难道你也是个吃货么
Hold on, are you a foodie, too?
我是红酒
What I am is a lover of fine wine,
佳肴和芭蕾舞爱好者
delightful cuisine and the ballet.
喜爱程度不分先后
In any order you pick.
边开会边跳舞就算了
Well, I don't think we can have dancers at the meeting.
不伴舞  但要做这个  那除非你懂烹饪
No, we can't. Which means unless you know how to cook,
否则我们得找个世界级大厨
we need to find ourselves a world class chef
而且还要快
and we need to find it fast.
你觉得这个怎么样  迈克和我之前刚刚
What about this: Mike and I just met with
为准备我们的婚礼见了一个世界级法餐大厨
a world class, French-trained chef to cater our wedding.
- 我是说  如果他刚好有时间 -定下他吧
-I mean, if he's available then-- - Book him.
你不想多听我讲讲他的经历
Well don't you wanna hear more about his--
瑞秋  如果我连你的选择都信不过
Rachel, if I can't trust your taste in pairings,
-我还能信谁的呢  -你在说什么
- I can't trust anyone's. - What are you talking about?
我还没有和你道谢过  但是你知道
I never thanked you for this, but you knew
我和你爸爸会很合拍
your father and I would be a great fit.
而且如果不是你想办法让我在被炒后和他见面
And if you hadn't set me up with him after I was fired,
我都不知道我该怎么办
I don't know what I would have done.
我去预定厨师
I'll book the chef.
既然你已经打过电话
I assume from the fact that you called,
那一定拿到我们的圣诞大礼了
you got our Christmas present.
我没找你  我打电话找了哈维・斯佩克特
I didn't call you, I called Harvey Specter.
但他找了我  而我决定要和你聊聊
Well, he called me. And I wanted to come
以防你以为可以背着我
have a little chat with you before you got it into your head
跟哈维搭成协议
that you could go behind my back
而不对错误行为进行承认
and cut a deal without an admission of guilt.
-什么  -听着
- What? - Look, I don't give a shit
我不在乎你提的价格是多少
how much you offered,
你没法花钱让自己抽身
you're not gonna buy your way out of this thing
然后把这件事掩盖下来
without telling the world what you did.
我觉得你不知道和解这两个字意味着什么
I don't think you understand what the word settlement means.
我知道他对你来说意味着什么
I understand what it means to you,
我只是不在乎
I just don't give a shit.
-一个亿  -并公开承认犯错
- One hundred million. - With an admission of guilt.
好啊  合同给我签
Sure, where do I sign?
你听着
Listen to me.
一个亿是这个公司有史以来的最大一笔支出
$100 million is the biggest payout this company's ever made.
不是的  因为我不答应
No, it's not because I'm not taking it.
你有病吗
What is wrong with you?
我可以直接付给你的客户  让他们的生活
I'm willing to cut your clients a check
焕然一新  而你却笨得看不到这点
that'll change their lives and you're too stupid to see it.
我所看到的是  只要案子多拖一天
Here's what I see: Every day this case drags on,
你的股价就多受一天拖累
your stock is gonna take a hit.
而且季度股东大会时
And every quarter when the board meets,
这会是你无法回避的第一个问题
that's gonna be their first question
而且是你最头疼的问题
and your biggest God damn headache.
所以我们真正要解决的问题是
So the real question is are you ready
你到底要不要为你曾经做过的负责
to take responsibility for what you did or not?
我看到你盛装回归大律所
I see you wore your power suit for your return to the majors.
如果你要出席洋基体育场
You gonna play in Yankee Stadium,
你最好穿好制服
you gotta wear the pinstripes.
怎么样了
How'd it go?
挺好的  他简直按着我们的剧本走
Good. He did exactly what we thought he would.
报低价  骂我蠢
Tried to lowball me, called me an idiot
然后把我赶出来
and then kicked me out.
他报价多少
How high did he go?
一个亿
A hundred million.
啥
What?
没事  只是我能让他开到两亿
Nothing, it's just I would've gotten him up to two.
是你叫我别还价
And how exactly would you have done that
那还怎么做到呢
when you told me not to counter?
我更能吓住人  我只要出现人就会自动投降
I'm more intimidating. I walk into a room, people cave.
-这是天赐的礼物  -我觉得你离开
- It's a gift. - I think it's a gift
-才是对他们的大礼  -可我给你的大礼
- when you leave the room. - My gift to you
是帮你收拾把我扯进来的
was saving your ass when you screwed the pooch
这个烂摊子
by involving me in this case.
我说真的  哈维  我很感激你参与进这件事
Seriously, Harvey, I appreciate you rolling with this thing.
尤其是我还随意发挥了
Especially when I had to improvise.
别担心  事实是
Don't worry about it. The truth is,
我真的很珍惜能够和你再次共事的机会
I like getting the chance to work with you again.
还有  别告诉瑞秋  我喜欢这超额的风险
Besides, don't tell Rachel, I like the added risk.
-我知道  -你怎么知道
- Oh, I know. - How do you know?
因为你告诉我的
'Cause you told me.
"生活高一尺  我却高一丈"
"Life's like this, but I like this."
把我当什么了  卢克・贝里
What am I, Luke Perry?
-有时候  -不过我要走了
- Sometimes. - Look, I gotta go.
因为这个混蛋一个小时后就会
'Cause this asshole's gonna be back in my office in an hour,
来我办公室背着你和我做交易
trying to cut a deal with me behind your back.
天呐
Oh, my God.
-这真是太棒了  -你真这么觉得
- This is amazing. - You really think so?
我知道  这把法律分析与
I know so. It's the perfect legal analysis
报告呈现完美地结合在一起
combined with the perfect presentation.
那你不觉得杰西卡不在这里这件事
So, you don't think the fact that Jessica isn't here--
杰西爱去哪卡去哪卡
Jessica Schmessica.
卡莉一定会大吃一惊的
Carly's gonna be blown away.
我真该现在就给你们俩升职
I should promote you both right now.
-真的吗  -当然不是
- Will you? - No.
-问下无妨  -好了  我们还有些时间
- Worth a try. - Okay, we have some time.
我一个小时后回来这见你们俩
So I'll meet you both back here in an hour.
-你要去哪  -要清清肠胃
- Where are you going? - Gonna go have a prunie.
要为这九道菜腾出地方
Wanna clean out the pipes for the nine course meal.
迈克・罗斯
Mike Ross.
-什么事  -我是克雷格・赛德尔
- Yes? - I'm Craig Seidel.
什么  你来干嘛
What? What are you doing here?
我想知道你到底在搞什么鬼
I wanna know what the hell you're doing.
什么叫我搞什么鬼
What you mean, what am I doing?
我是说你提起150件诉讼  而非一件
I mean, you filed 150 suits, not just one.
詹姆斯・帕默要逐一应战
And James Palmer's gonna fight each one of them.
这意味着这件事会旷日持久
Which means this thing is gonna drag on forever.
只要他一去找哈维
And we're gonna drop the hammer on him
我们就能给他致命一击
as soon as he gets to Harvey's.
我不想再见到你
Now I don't wanna see you again
直到第一次听证会再见到你
until I meet you for the first time at that hearing.
别想就这么走了
Don't you walk away from me.
我雇哈维工作  而他却违背我的意愿
I hired Harvey to do a job, he farmed it out to you
外包给你  你总他妈要听我讲讲
against my will and you're gonna God damn listen to me.
不  你没有雇哈维
No, you didn't hire Harvey.
你之前还给我未婚妻找麻烦
You tried to mess with my fiancée's life and you're lucky
我们没有让你取消律师资格算你走运
we didn't have you disbarred.
所以不要来我工作的地方
So instead of coming to my place of work
骚扰我  你还是滚回你的窝
and harassing me, why don't you go back
等结束了我们会告诉你
to your hole and we'll tell you it's done.
行啊  但你的机会不多了
Okay, but your window's closing.
这事短时间内不会结束
This doesn't get wrapped up soon,
你成为律师的想法可以打住了
your shot at being a lawyer is over.
如果你要求提高诉讼金额
If you're gonna bankroll a suit,
你至少要有胆自己来谈
at least have the balls to negotiate it yourself.
我就当做你对提议不满意
I take it you didn't like the offer.
承认过错可不是提议
Admission of guilt isn't an offer.
那是自杀
It's suicide.
这是迈克・罗斯的案子  他说的算
It's Mike Ross' case, it's his call.
扯淡  迈克・罗斯就是个法律诊所员工
Bullshit. Mike Ross is some clinic worker.
你是哈维・斯佩克特  而据我所知
You're Harvey Specter. And from what I hear about you,
你根本就不关心过错
you don't give a shit about guilt.
没错  我是不关心
You're right, I don't.
那你就告诉我多少钱
So why don't you tell me how much
-能摆平这件事  -五亿
- it's gonna take to make this go away. - 500 million.
乘2就十亿了  你疯了吧
Half a billion dollars? Are you insane?
你毒害自己的雇员  帕默先生
You poisoned your employees, Mr. Palmer.
你没在监狱都算幸运的
You're lucky you're not in prison.
-两亿  -不行
- 200 million. - No.
-三亿  -不行
- 300 - No.
这样吧  三点五亿收工
Okay, make it 350 and call it a day.
五亿  一个子儿都不能少
500. Not a penny less.
这样的话就不谈了
In that case, make it zero
因为你刚证实了我今早就开始怀疑的事情
because you just confirmed what I suspected since this morning.
你挑一个这么确切的数字好让我的股价暴跌
You picked the exact number to make my stock take a nosedive
我们都知道谁会受益
and we both know who benefits from that.
克雷格・赛德尔
Craig Seidel.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
那我猜你也不知道迈克・罗斯
Then I guess you also don't know that Mike Ross
刚和道德委员会达成约定
just got an appointment with the ethics board
这样这笔交易就是违法的
and it's a crime to trade this for that.
这意味着你的诉讼也结束了
Which means your lawsuit is over.
那我就做点别的
Then I'll do something else.
你认为你偷了赛德尔公司的技术
You think I won't go after you
我不能追究你盗窃吗
for stealing technology from Seidel's company?
你证明不了我做过什么
You have no proof I did anything.
我证明不了但他可以
No, but he does
我才不在乎他的婚姻
and I don't give a shit about his marriage,
而且我会让他出面作证
and I'm going to make him come forward.
他的婚姻
His marriage?
他告诉你他是在顾忌这个
Is that what he told you this is about?
我倒是有些消息给你  斯佩克特先生
Well, I've got news for you, Mr. Specter,
他不肯出面
the reason he hasn't come forward
根本不是因为他的婚姻
has nothing to do with his marriage.
那你去查查他到底为什么不愿出面
So, why don't you go find out what's what.
我有种预感等你查到
And I got a feeling when you do,
就会立刻撤销这件案子
you'll drop this case by the morning.
-你好  -你好
- Hey. - Hey.
你逃离展示的速度太快
You ran out of the presentation so quickly,
我都没来得及问你的想法
I didn't get to ask what you thought.
我要去上课  但我觉得进行的很顺利
I had to get to class, but I thought it went great.
-路易呢  -他开心死了
- What about Louis? - He was over the Moon.
我相信你回来他会很高兴的
I'm sure he's glad to have you back.
我也很高兴回来
I'm glad to be back.
-我应该  -跟我爸一起工作感觉怎么样
- Well, I should, uh-- - What was it like working with my dad?
你说这个搭配非常棒而我想知道
You said it was a great pairing and I was just wondering--
-你错过了什么  -是的
- What you were missing. - Yes.
你错过了一个十分智慧
You were missing a brilliant,
不知疲倦  可爱迷人而又风趣幽默的男人
tireless, sweet, funny, charming man.
他也是我见过最棒的诉讼律师
who may also be the best litigator I've ever seen.
也许你没明白我的问题
Maybe you didn't understand my question.
我是问和我爸赞恩一起工作的感觉
I was asking what it was like to work with Zane,
-不是他的合伙人卡尔多  -瑞秋  我认真的
- not Kaldor. - Rachel, I'm serious.
我在那的时候跟你爸爸学到了很多
I learned a lot about your father while I was there
我要告诉你  一切都很棒
and I'm telling you, it was all good.
那他的脾气呢
What about his temper?
好吧  也许不是一切都好
Well, maybe it wasn't all good.
晚上愉快
Well, good night.
我还知道他一件事
One more thing I learned about him.
他不止爱你  他尊敬你
He doesn't just love you, he respects you.
-你怎么知道  -他向你提供工作的时候
- How would you know that-- - When he offered you that job,
他喜气洋洋
he was beaming.
他跟办公室里的每个人说他聪明的宝贝女儿
He told everyone in the office that his brilliant baby girl
就要跟他一起工作了
was gonna work for us and she was gonna
而她会击败我们所有人
blow us all to smithereens.
-他这么说的  -瑞秋  我没有告诉你
- He said that? - Rachel, I didn't tell you that
是不想你伤心
to make you feel bad.
你虽然没接受他的邀请  他也能承受
He was okay that you didn't take his offer.
这没有让我伤心
It doesn't make me feel bad.
而让我感觉更好
It makes me feel great.
-他在吗  -不在  他有事走了
- Is he in? - No, he had to run out.
那行  你帮我个忙
All right, do me a favor,
他回来后告诉他我得找他谈谈
just tell him I need to talk to him when he gets back.
你介意我问一下什么事吗
You mind if I ask what it's about?
我刚和卡莉・唐纳休通过电话
I just got off the phone with Carly Donahue.
路易  怎么了  瑞秋说挺顺利的
Louis, what happened? Rachel said that it went great.
我之前也这么想  但后来她给我打电话
I thought it did, too, but then she called me
说如果下次她想跟我和哈维
and said that the next time she asks for a meeting
见面  她最好能跟我和哈维见面
with me and Harvey, she better get a goddamn meeting
而不是派两只虾兵蟹将
with me and Harvey instead of two nobodies.
-你怎么跟她说的  -我告诉她你怎么敢
- What did you tell her? - I told her how dare she
这么说我两个心头宝
talk about my superstars like that.
能遇到她们是她的荣幸
She's lucky to have them.
路易  说得真好  你真棒
Louis, that's great. Good for you.
她把我们解雇了  唐娜
She fired us, Donna.
路易  我很抱歉  听着  这不是你的错
Oh, Louis, I'm so sorry. Look, this isn't your fault.
-你又想不到  -没事
- You couldn't have known. - It's okay.
我得回家去了
I just need to go home.
该死
Shit.
没事的  唐娜
It's okay, Donna.
-这也不是你的错  -不  这是我的错
- It's not your fault, either. - Yes, it is.
我可是唐娜  我应该想到的
I'm Donna, I should have known.
或许吧  但你总说
Maybe, but you always say
是人都会出乱子
part of being human is messing up sometimes
你也许是唐娜  但你也是人
and you may be Donna, but you're still human.
该死
Holy shit.
你蓄势待发了
You are ready.
奥利佛
Oliver.
你来这儿有什么事
Hey, what are you doing here?
我想知道我之前是否看错你了
I want to know if I was wrong about you.
-你在说什么  -我想知道
- What are you talking about? - I wanna know
你是否利用此案想重回皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所
if you're using this case to get back to Pearson Specter.
奥利佛  我们谈过此事
Oliver, we talked about this.
我以为你了解我不是那样的人
I thought you understood that's not who I am.
我也这么认为  但后来我一想
I thought so, too, but then I got to thinking.
你这么长时间把好多人骗得团团转
You fooled so many people for so long.
如果你现在也在骗我呢
What if you're fooling me now?
因为你告诉我你还在皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所时
Because you said Pearson Specter would never take on
他们绝不会接这种案子
a case like this when you were there before.
没错  因为他们绝不想在一场公司诉讼中
Yeah, because they never wanted to be on the wrong side
站错了队
of a corporate lawsuit.
那现在他们为什么选择错的一队
Then why are they on the wrong side of one now?
-奥利佛  -拜托  别骗我  迈克
- Oliver-- - Please, don't lie to me, Mike.
跟我说实话
Just tell me what's going on.
说来话长  但我们接这个案子
It's a long story, but we brought the suit
这样我就能进律师协会
so that i could get into the Bar.
所以你骗了纳森  只不过不是他想的那样
So you were lying to Nathan, only not about what he thought.
-听我说  -我不听
- Listen to me-- - I'm not gonna listen
你得告诉他到底发生了什么
and you need to tell him what's going on.
我不能这么做  我说我不会
I can't do that and I wasn't lying to him
重回之前的律所  我没有骗他
when I said I'm not going back to my old firm.
我说我很重视这些人的生活
I wasn't lying to him when I said
我也没有说谎
these people's lives matter to me
我说我在意你会成为一名怎样的律师
and I wasn't lying to either one of you when I said
我也没骗你们任何一个人
I care about what kind of lawyer you're gonna be.
如果你在意我会成为怎样一名律师
Well, if you care what kind of lawyer I'm going to be,
那就做个好榜样
set the right example
因为纳森需要知道事情的真相
because you owe it to Nathan to tell him the truth.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hey.
-这是什么
- What's this?
这是我所有的年鉴
It's every yearbook I've ever had.
那晚我们一起看你的年鉴真的很温馨
It was so nice doing it with yours the other night
我想今晚我们可以一起来看我的
I thought maybe tonight we could do it with mine.
路易  怎么了
Louis, what's wrong?
没什么  今天  有点不顺
Nothing's wrong. I, uh--had a bad day
我想和你谈谈此事
and I wanted to talk to you about it.
但你费事做了这些
But you went to all this trouble
我不想来烦你
and I don't want to bring you down.
路易  我的年鉴又跑不了
Louis, my yearbooks are always gonna be here.
而且聊聊对你来说很重要的工作
And hearing about something as important to you as your work
不会烦到我的
isn't going to bring me down.
这只会让我们更亲密
It's going to bring us closer.
你确定吗  因为我好多天都不好过
Are you sure because I have a lot of bad days at work.
这就更有理由这么做了
Which is all the more reason
你需要回家后能有人让你舒服些
for you to have someone to make you feel better at home.
好吧  但说起来有点长
Okay, but it's kind of a long story.
那你先坐好  我给你拿杯喝的
Well then you sit right here, I'll go make you a drink
然后你就能对我一诉衷肠
and then you can tell me all about it.
你知道我想喝什么吗
You know what I'm in the mood for?
我还说不上  但我确定荷产桃味杜松子酒和
I can't tell which one yet, but I'm pretty sure its either
上好的冷梅酒  两者选其一
a Peach Schnapps or a nice, cold Prunie.
你真的越来越懂我了  对吗
You really are getting to know me, aren't you?
那当然
I sure am.
我的天  你来这儿干嘛
Jesus Christ. What are you doing here?
你们不是告诉我要离你远点
You guys told me to stay away from you.
没错  那是在我和你的伙计
Yeah, that was before I had a chat
詹姆斯・帕默谈过之前
with your buddy James Palmer.
听着  我不认识什么詹姆斯・帕默
Look, I don't even know James Palmer,
-所以不管他说了什么  -他不用说什么
- so whatever he said-- - He didn't have to say anything,
他只要指一指就好
all he had to do was point.
那又怎样  一个用我名字注册的离岸账户
So what? This is an off-shore account in my name.
一个存了三十万美金的离岸账户
An off-shore account with $300,000 in it,
正好发生在所谓的极速公司
deposited exactly a day after Velocity supposedly
窃取你技术之后
stole your technology.
我会计告诉我要把特定收益另存
I was told by my accountant to shelter certain earnings.
胡扯  你根本没有这些收益
Bullshit. You don't have those kind of earnings.
你不是因为你结婚了才想低调处理此事
And you didn't have to keep this quiet because you're married.
你是因为牵涉其中才这么做
You kept it quiet because you're in on it.
我之前牵涉其中
I was in on it.
我看到挣脱的机会  还能从中获利
I saw a chance to jump ship and get paid in the process.
但事实是  他们毁了我的计划
But instead, they pulled the job
在那账户中放了足够的钱来拉我下水
and put just enough money in that account to implicate me.
-你个混蛋  -拜托  我的员工
- You piece of shit. - Please, my employees
会因为我而失业
are gonna lose their jobs because of me.
我们得把官司打下去  把技术拿回来
We need to keep this suit going and get that technology back.
不  伙计
Nuh-uh, buddy.
你根本不在乎你的员工
You don't give a shit about your employees
我也根本不在乎你
and I don't give a shit about you.
-协议就此作罢  -你不能这么做
- This deal is done. - You can't do this.
不  我能  我之前没有筹码  但现在有了
Yes, I can and I didn't have leverage before, but I have it now.
所以你不仅要给迈克安排面试
So you're not just getting Mike an interview,
你还要说服每个投反对票的人
you're gonna block anyone who tries to vote no.
如果你不这么做  你老板就会
And if you don't, your boss is gonna get
收到一份匿名检举说你出卖商业机密
an anonymous tip that you sold trade secrets.
我会确保让他收到
And I'm gonna make sure to send this along with it.
你是我的律师  你为我工作
You're my attorney. You work for me.
-你不能这么做  -我不为你工作
- You can't do that. - I don't work for you.
记得吗  克雷格  我就是这么挖坑的
Remember, Craig? That's how I set it up.
我们律师协会见
See you at the Bar.